

A.Selvakumar Front-End Developer

https://blackyselva1997.github.io/Resume/

- (L) +91 7200133526
- selvam17196@gmail.co
- https://github.com/blacky selva1997
- (4) Male
- 28.08.1997
- (•) 4/59-1, Poovarasan Kovil st,Thippanampatti, Tenkasi-627808.



Objective

Shor-term:

My goal is to become a skilled full-stack web developer in the next two years by learning frontend and back- end technologies, improving my coding skills, and problem-solving abilities. Long-term:

I aspire to be a manager for the long term.



Education

ARULMIGU SENTHILANDAVAR POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE Diploma Automobile Engineering

I have Like the Laptop spare parts.

May 2014 - June 2016



Work experience

FABVEY TECHNOLOGIES

Oct 2022 - May 2023

I am training to become a Front-end developer.

Training for 7 months.

MICROLUX SYSTEMS

2018 - 2022

2016 - 2017

System Service Engineering.

3.5 Years

MURUGAPPA TII-IIIC

Machine Operator

1 Years



Skills

Language	Tamil, English.
Computer	MS Office.
Web Design	HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ES6, Node.js, React.js, Sass.
Others	System Service Engineering.



Projects

WebSite Design:

- 1. Restaurantly. (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/Restaurantly-Project/)
 - In used [HTML,CSS]
- 2. Graphbit. (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/Graphbit-Project/)

In used - [HTML,CSS,BOOTSTRAP]

3. Vel-Electroincs. (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/Vel-Electronics-Project/) In used - [HTML,CSS,BOOTSTRAP,JAVASCRIPT]

JavaScript MiniProject:

- 1. BMI. (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/BMI-Calculate-DOM-Mini-Project/)
- 2. Digital-Clock (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/Digital-Clock-Mini-Project/)
- 3. Facebook-Sign-Login (https://blackyselva1997.github.io/swiggy-signup/)